[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "And just for the hell of it, how I'm doing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "just", "for", "the", "hell", "of", "it", ",", "how", "I", "'m", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "You're pretty focused.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "pretty", "focused", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "I don't Tweet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "Tweet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "So you didn't repeat very often?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "did", "n't", "repeat", "very", "often", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "What do you think about the way that television has evolved since your daily show stopped?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "about", "the", "way", "that", "television", "has", "evolved", "since", "your", "daily", "show", "stopped", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, you know, it's hard for me to -- I don't want to criticize them because I took a lot of heat.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "for", "me", "to", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "criticize", "them", "because", "I", "took", "a", "lot", "of", "heat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Would you like that to be your epitaph, Phil?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "that", "to", "be", "your", "epitaph", ",", "Phil", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "ONAHUE: Well, it wasn't my idea.", "answer_tokens": ["ONAHUE", ":", "Well", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "my", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phil"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "That it would be strange if you did approve of it all in a sense, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "it", "would", "be", "strange", "if", "you", "did", "approve", "of", "it", "all", "in", "a", "sense", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "What was the reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Everybody thought their kids would catch it if they watched it.", "answer_tokens": ["Everybody", "thought", "their", "kids", "would", "catch", "it", "if", "they", "watched", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mohamed Ali"]}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "If I could I let you do one again tomorrow, what would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "I", "let", "you", "do", "one", "again", "tomorrow", ",", "what", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "We had a very good program with Mohamed Ali.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "a", "very", "good", "program", "with", "Mohamed", "Ali", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlo"]}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Which you just don't get that package, do you, very often?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "you", "just", "do", "n't", "get", "that", "package", ",", "do", "you", ",", "very", "often", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Marlo did a book titled \"The Right Words, At The Right Time\".", "answer_tokens": ["Marlo", "did", "a", "book", "titled", "``", "The", "Right", "Words", ",", "At", "The", "Right", "Time", "''", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Each also brought pride and boldness to young black males, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Each", "also", "brought", "pride", "and", "boldness", "to", "young", "black", "males", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Completely.", "answer_tokens": ["Completely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "What do you have make of the Rick Santorum surge?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "have", "make", "of", "the", "Rick", "Santorum", "surge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "And one of many.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "one", "of", "many", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Guantanamo, you mean?", "question_tokens": ["Guantanamo", ",", "you", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "And this is an abject, miserable failure that he should be lambasted for?", "question_tokens": ["And", "this", "is", "an", "abject", ",", "miserable", "failure", "that", "he", "should", "be", "lambasted", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "He's calling for a nanny government.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "calling", "for", "a", "nanny", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "What have you become?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "become", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Nobody runs around saying I'm a liberal, I'm a liberal.", "answer_tokens": ["Nobody", "runs", "around", "saying", "I", "'m", "a", "liberal", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "liberal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "When you look back, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "It was certainly true.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "certainly", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What did I say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "I", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "She didn't do too badly, but.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "did", "n't", "do", "too", "badly", ",", "but", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "What do you think of Oprah?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Oprah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I think Oprah has risen to a level in the stratosphere unknown to all of us.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Oprah", "has", "risen", "to", "a", "level", "in", "the", "stratosphere", "unknown", "to", "all", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Why do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, I think she's - she's a compelling personality.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "she", "'s", "-", "she", "'s", "a", "compelling", "personality", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Is it the same?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "same", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Well -", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "-"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Look at my own early history.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "at", "my", "own", "early", "history", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "I mean that's a pretty good endorsement, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "that", "'s", "a", "pretty", "good", "endorsement", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Hampshire"]}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "I suppose the one big unanswered question is why can he not break through this kind of what is becoming almost mythical 25 percent barrier of support in his own party?", "question_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "the", "one", "big", "unanswered", "question", "is", "why", "can", "he", "not", "break", "through", "this", "kind", "of", "what", "is", "becoming", "almost", "mythical", "25", "percent", "barrier", "of", "support", "in", "his", "own", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "He's going to break through that barrier I hope and believe in a couple days in New Hampshire.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "going", "to", "break", "through", "that", "barrier", "I", "hope", "and", "believe", "in", "a", "couple", "days", "in", "New", "Hampshire", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["25 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How has it been for you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "it", "been", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I don't think we'll ever get over it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "'ll", "ever", "get", "over", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Gabrielle Giffords has been shot, presumed dead and other people have been gunned down, what were you thinking when this was all unfurling?", "question_tokens": ["Gabrielle", "Giffords", "has", "been", "shot", ",", "presumed", "dead", "and", "other", "people", "have", "been", "gunned", "down", ",", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "when", "this", "was", "all", "unfurling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I was thinking it was a nightmare and I was going to wake up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "thinking", "it", "was", "a", "nightmare", "and", "I", "was", "going", "to", "wake", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gabrielle Giffords"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "I mean, you, I know John, you first discovered your daughter was dead, was told, did they get (INAUDIBLE) the person who did this?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", ",", "I", "know", "John", ",", "you", "first", "discovered", "your", "daughter", "was", "dead", ",", "was", "told", ",", "did", "they", "get", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "the", "person", "who", "did", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "And did it give you any kind of comfort that they had?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "it", "give", "you", "any", "kind", "of", "comfort", "that", "they", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "It definitely it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "definitely", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Was it cathartic in any sense?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "cathartic", "in", "any", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "It was very difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "very", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Is it hard to reconcile your faith when something like this happens?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "hard", "to", "reconcile", "your", "faith", "when", "something", "like", "this", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "No, not for me.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Let's talk about the person that did this, Jared Loughner, what are your views of him?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "talk", "about", "the", "person", "that", "did", "this", ",", "Jared", "Loughner", ",", "what", "are", "your", "views", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Well, we do feel that he was mentally disturbed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "do", "feel", "that", "he", "was", "mentally", "disturbed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jared Loughner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "And if people want to help, what do they do?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "people", "want", "to", "help", ",", "what", "do", "they", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "They go to christinataylorgreen.org and we have a web site.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "go", "to", "christinataylorgreen.org", "and", "we", "have", "a", "web", "site", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]